David McNeary

Email: mcneary.david@gmail.com | Phone: 541-892-4133 | Los Angeles, CA 90066

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidmcneary/ | Github: https://github.com/dmcneary |

Portfolio: https://dmcneary.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a strong interest in Javascript solutions

ATTRIBUTES			TECHNICAL SKILLS	
0	Very quick to adapt to new environments and situations Priority towards detailed attentive results	0 0 0	HTML5 & CSS3 ES6 & jQuery React & React Router	
•	Proficiency and constant yearning for knowledge	\$	Node.js with Express.js server MySQL & mongoDB databases	
٥	Eagerness to learn, implement, and expand upon existing procedures	© ©	Sequelize & Mongoose ORMs Server-side templating (Handlebars.js)	
٥	Experience with rapidly deploying websites and webapps with Github Pages and Heroku	٥	Git with Github	

EXPERIENCE

Cynergy Cycles Santa Monica, CA 90404	♡	Helped to implement and train staff on new service menus, coordinated with remote co-workers at other locations for consistency
Service Tech Lead	\odot	Improved personal mechanical aptitude through sponsored attendance
July 2017 to Present		at Specialized Bicycle Components University - hydraulic brake systems, electronic drivetrains, static suspension tuning and service
Ride Brooklyn	\odot	Heavily revised and implemented a comprehensive service menu,
Brooklyn, NY 11206		accounting for competitors' rates and perceived quality of service
Service Manager	\odot	Worked with staff across two stores to coordinate best practices
July 2016 to Present		towards sales and technical support
UrbanStems		
New York, NY 10016	\odot	Oversaw expedited delivery of gifts throughout Manhattan and
Delivery Lead		Washington, DC by bicycle, delicately and efficiently
November 2015 to July 2016	\Diamond	Local & remote dispatching and courier support
NYC Velo		
New York, NY 10036		Created rental fleet maintenance schedule and procedures
Service Manager		Trained employees on new POS system and procedures (Lightspeed)
March 2014 to August 2015		

EDUCATION

- O UCLA Extension Coding Boot Camp, 2018-Present
- University of Oregon Photography, 2007-2010
- Portland State University Arts Studies, 2010-2011